{
    "subject": "Kamal_Haasan",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Thevar_Magan",
    "human_readable": "Kamal Haasan acted in the film Thevar Magan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9782565832138062,
            "question": "Did Kamal Haasan star in a film called Thevar Magan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9395185708999634,
            "question": "In which film did Kamal Haasan have a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9217290282249451,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Kamal Haasan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9043287038803101,
            "question": "Who acted in the film Thevar Magan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8795212507247925,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Kamal Haasan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8675955533981323,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Kamal Haasan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8371308445930481,
            "question": "What film did Kamal Haasan act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8091192245483398,
            "question": "Is Kamal Haasan an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.805953323841095,
            "question": "What is the title of the film starring Kamal Haasan mentioned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7861818075180054,
            "question": "Which actor appeared in Thevar Magan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kamal Haasan acted in the film Thevar Magan.",
            "html": "yago_3083_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film starring Kamal Haasan mentioned?",
            "html": "yago_3083_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kamal Haasan an actor?",
            "html": "yago_3083_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Kamal Haasan act in?",
            "html": "yago_3083_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3083_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Kamal Haasan's role in the film \"Thevar Magan,\" including details about his performance and the film's success. Therefore, the triple stating that Kamal Haasan acted in the film \"Thevar Magan\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}